[{"question":"which object is bigger?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The porcelain cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium metal cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the medium metal cube lighter than the small RedUnknown cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small RedUnknown cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium bamboo cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small RedUnknown cube travel to quadrant \u2162?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2162?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium metal cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium bamboo cube collide with the small RedUnknown cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium bamboo cube collide with the small porcelain cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube and the small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The small porcelain cube and the medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the medium metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small redunknown cube and the medium bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The wall and the small redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The wall and the small porcelain cube"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Will the medium bamboo cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0}]